=A Love Journal= =Episode 10=
= A Love Journal = = الحلقة 10 =
You can't go with another man.
لا يمكنك الذهاب مع رجل آخر.
Why can't I go with another man?
لماذا لا يمكنني الذهاب مع رجل آخر؟
If your mom takes a video of us and sends it to my mom,
إذا التقطت والدتك فيديو لنا وأرسلته إلى أمي ،
my mom will know it.
أمي ستعرف ذلك.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Anyway, you broke the agreement first.
على أي حال ، لقد خرقت الاتفاقية أولاً.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll go.
سأذهب.
But you must let me decide the time and place.
لكن يجب أن تدعني أقرر الزمان والمكان.
It's my mom.
إنها أمي.
What do we do?
ماذا نفعل؟
Can't be this week.
لا يمكن أن يكون هذا الأسبوع.
Tell her I'm on a business trip.
أخبرها أنني في رحلة عمل.
Then
ثم
you will not be the perfect son-in-law in her eyes anymore.
لن تكون الصهر المثالي في عينيها بعد الآن.
Or tell her you're on a business trip.
أو أخبرها أنك في رحلة عمل.
No, I won't.
لا ، لن أفعل.
She'll fix me.
سوف تصلحني.
What about
ماذا عن
telling her
يخبرها
we are traveling?
نحن نسافر؟
Traveling
سفر
in the bedroom?
في غرفة النوم؟
Then do you have another way?
إذن هل لديك طريقة أخرى؟
It's all your fault.
هذا كله خطأك.
I have a way.
لدي طريقة.
Mom.
أم.
Sui.
سوي.
Why is the sky bright there?
لماذا السماء مشرقة هناك؟
Gu Shen brought me to Paris.
أحضرني قو شين إلى باريس.
Why did you go to Paris?
لماذا ذهبت الى باريس؟
Aren't we going to have dinner with our relatives this weekend?
ألن نتناول العشاء مع أقاربنا في نهاية هذا الأسبوع؟
Mom.
أم.
Don't blame her.
لا تلومها.
I brought her here.
أحضرتها هنا.
I want her to get the feeling of romance.
أريدها أن تشعر بالرومانسية.
Romance?
رومانسي؟
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
- When will you be back? - Mom.
- متى ستعود؟  - أم.
We'll go back next week.
سنعود الأسبوع المقبل.
I'll make up for the dinner for you.
سوف أعوض عن العشاء من أجلك.
Good, good.
جيد جيد.
Mom.
أم.
It's a bad connection.
إنه اتصال سيء.
I gotta hang up.
يجب أن أغلق المكالمة.
Bye.
وداعا.
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
Give me a hand.
ساعدني.
My job is done here, right?
عملي تم هنا ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Take away the backdrop.
يسلب الخلفية.
Bye.
وداعا.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
I'm smart, right?
أنا ذكي ، صحيح؟
If it weren't for my cleverness,
لولا ذكاءي ،
you wouldn't be able to hold on even for one more second.
لن تكون قادرًا على الصمود ولو لثانية واحدة أخرى.
Why don't you talk about how fat you are?
لماذا لا تتحدث عن كم أنت سمين؟
Who's fat?
المتواجدون السمين؟
Why don't you talk about how weak you are?
لماذا لا تتحدث عن مدى ضعفك؟
Wanna try it?
هل تريد تجربتها؟
(Huzhou Youth Volunteer) The car broke down again?
(متطوع شباب هوتشو) تعطلت السيارة مرة أخرى؟
Okay, I'm ready to go now.
حسنًا ، أنا جاهز للذهاب الآن.
That's it.
هذا هو.
Let's talk about it when we meet.
دعنا نتحدث عن ذلك عندما نلتقي.
Bye.
وداعا.
How come you walk without making any sound?
كيف تمشي دون أن تصدر أي صوت؟
You're going out? But it's the weekend.
ستخرج؟  لكنها عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
I'm going to do volunteer activities.
سأقوم بأنشطة تطوعية.
I ordered a taxi.
طلبت سيارة أجرة.
I gotta go.
أنا سأذهب.
(Mind traffic rules, and go with courtesy)
(ضع في اعتبارك قواعد المرور ، واذهب بلطف)
Hello. Take a look.
مرحبًا.  إلق نظرة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
I'm on Guangyu Street.
أنا في شارع قوانغيو.
Okay.
تمام.
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
Gu Shen said to bring me something.
قال قو شين لإحضار شيء لي.